Here we go!
We're starting the Nogizaka Kouji!
I'm Sugawara Sugawara
And I'm Morihira
And here we have Nogizaka-chan!
She's really taking care of something
What is it?
Oh! It rang!
Cute, isn't it?
Alright then, please announce today's
project!
Yes!
The life of my life is being extended!
We're in the middle of the extension!
Yes, yes, we're in the middle of the
extension.
There was also the first half, but it
seems that there are still a lot of
famous words that we couldn't introduce.
I would like to hear the famous words
that have influenced everyone's lives
even during the extension.
Nao, did you participate in the
extension?
I was looking at the main story a little
bit, but everyone was pretty serious.
There was a lot of comments from
different angles, so I thought it might
be a little different when I submitted
it.
There were a lot of comments from
different angles, so I was looking
forward to it.
Then it might be okay.
It might be okay. Good.
The first person to introduce the comment
is Aya.
This is the comment that pierced Aya's
heart.
This is the phrase that stuck in my mind.
I want you to live more easily and
freely.
Who gave you this phrase?
It's Arno.
I'm so cute.
You said it a lot.
I was looking at you.
It's still the same.
She said it quite frequently for a while.
I said it.
Yes, I did. After that, it became really
easy for me.
Really? I'm so happy.
It became really easy for me.
Did you say that during the live show?
What kind of live show?
They said a lot of things to me.
That's true.
I think I was told that too.
What?
They said that.
They talked about it during the live
show.
I think I was told that too.
I think so too.
I don't think so.
How was it?
I was surprised.
I've been told a lot that I look like Nob
izaka since I was a child, and I thought
that I didn't want to be bound by that,
so I've been in the entertainment
industry since I was really young.
If you live as you please, that's fine. I
think I said it a lot.
I think she is the oldest in the five
seasons, and I have the impression that
she said a lot to the younger group.
Unexpectedly.
Please stand up.
It's not just Pongko-chan.
There is also a very older side.
I think she is cute.
Next, the member who will introduce the
famous words is Hii-tsun.
Here are the famous words that stuck in
Hii-tsun's heart.
It doesn't matter if it's ordinary.
Oh, I said it.
She said it.
Who said this?
This is something that should have been
done in the first year during the Nogiz
aka Kouji.
It's a word that Nagi Inoue gave me as a
present.
It's a word that was presented to me, but
I remember that I've been watching
seniors who are active in variety shows,
and I thought that some characters may be
necessary, and I'm really grateful that
they often say that their faces are like
adults, so I thought that I had to do it
firmly.
I thought I had to do it well, and I was
really talking about it, and I was saying
it properly, but while I was doing
something, I wanted you to like me as I
am, and now I'm having a lot of fun
talking about it in Nogichu, so it's
I can feel it.
It's really good to keep it as it is.
Because the people around us make this
world special.
So I want you to be relieved.
Thank you.
You're cute.
When you talk, your hands are like this.
But even if you keep it as it is, there
are many people who love you because you
are strong.
It's difficult.
It's hard. Even if you think you're
delivering it as it is, there are times
when it's not like that.
It's hard. I'm sure it's more of a
lifelong worry than being an idol.
I wonder how many years it's been.
Aruna said her favorite food at the
beginning was macaron.
What was it now?
What was it again?
Guts Pons
I love it
At first, I wanted to be an idol
But the fans were like, you can't do this
I was like, I can't do this anymore
You took off all your armor
That's right.
From the very beginning.
Next, we will introduce Yuna.
This is Yuna's favorite line.
Yuna's bangs are too cute, so I just
wanted to tell her that.
What is this?
This is...
Nagi-chan contacted me about how she felt
when she came to see the UNDERLIVE
concert.
She said,
Thank you for your hard work. I had a lot
of fun.
And she sent me this.
Even now, when I split my bangs, I still
remember it very much.
She didn't change the line just to tell
me this, but she added it.
She said she added it on her own.
Nagi's hair is long, so I like it very
much, and I especially like the ponytail
that separates the bangs.
Last year, he took a picture with me on a
tour.
Nagi and I often talk about hair.
We talk about our hairstyles.
It's so cute that it's so cute.
It's cute to contact each other, and it's
cute to tell each other that you like
each other.
The members don't do that much.
Moreover, I was surprised because I just
split my bangs rather than my hairstyle.
I was surprised, and I was confident that
we would be able to split up.
I think this was the reason why we had so
many members.
Nagi, are you watching this?
No, but I'm sure you are.
The next member to introduce us to is Sug
awara-san.
This is what Sugawara-san wrote in her
mind.
Here is the comment.
Senpai doesn't think like that.
Even if you do something,
I think you are doing your best.
So it's okay.
What is this comment?
This comment is from Lilia.
When I just became a vice captain,
I was in the same team with Lilia.
It was 3 vs 1.
We went to dinner together.
At that time, I was still a little scared
to say or act something while I was with
my seniors.
When I asked him what I should do, I
think Lilia said these words casually.
I think he's doing his best, so don't
think about anything negative, it's okay,
and he's been saying that all the time,
and it's been about a year and a half,
and when I talk to the members, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it
's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it
's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it
's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it
's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay, it's
What did you say after you became the
captain of the team?
I talked to Sakura about it.
She said that she was scared because
there were a lot of 3rd and 4th grade
students.
She encouraged me to be okay.
I was so happy that they cheered me up
and encouraged me to keep it bright.
They cheered me up and encouraged me to
keep it bright.
Rokkisei-chan kept telling us to do our
best so that Satsuki-san wouldn't be a nu
isance to us.
I was like, don't think about that and
just live your life to the fullest.
I'm so happy. Thank you.
Next up, we have Nao who will introduce
us to Nao's charming points.
You're such a cute person.
It's the 8th question.
You're aware of what she said, aren't
you?
Yes, I am.
She says it all the time.
I thought it was something else.
She has a strong point.
She says she has a strong point.
From the beginning, she used to love me a
lot.
But recently, she doesn't say it in
words.
But she says it.
Nao is like a little cheeky little
sister.
For me, that's really cute.
I don't like it.
I want to be like a cute girl.
I want to be like that.
That's how I want to get along with Nao.
Nao is thinking negatively about me.
I think I'm cute there.
I think so.
I'm selfish.
Do you often see that scene?
That's cute.
But I can't do it if I can't do it.
You are clear about that.
I'm doing my best to do it myself.
Yes, I'm doing my best.
There's something written on the document
that you received in advance.
It says,
What words have you been told recently?
It's just a casual conversation, isn't
it?
That's right.
When I'm at the end of a live show,
I'm like,
I'm going to see Rao-chan.
I'm dressed up next to him.
So,
When I'm at the end of a live show,
I'm like,
It can't be helped. He's so cute.
He says that to me.
But I want you to say it as it is.
Because you're 20 years old, right?
But I don't want to cry as an adult.
You don't want to cry?
That's good.
Until when?
Well, I think I'll say that in high
school.
Because it's your name.
Next, the member who will introduce her
famous lines is Nakanishi-san.
My famous line is this.
Please say it.
Here it is.
It's okay to be slow, and you can
practice anytime.
Who told you this?
This is from Satsuki Sugawara-san.
Do you remember this?
Yeah, I remember this.
Very clearly.
This is the phrase I used when I did the
musical for Sailor Moon.
When I was asked to do a musical for the
first time, I think I was the most punk
in Nagizaka in the past few years.
It was my first time doing a musical, and
I couldn't do anything because I couldn't
remember the lines and the movements.
Because of the movement, I couldn't do
anything anymore, and I caused a lot of
trouble to everyone in the organization.
At that time, Satsuki said,
No, it's okay. It's okay to be slow, so I
'll practice as much as I can.
At that time, Satsuki wasn't a captain,
of course, and he wasn't in a position to
be a vice captain.
I wasn't even in the position to do it.
But the strength of the words that came
out of Satsuki's heart
I thought I was really saved at that
time.
I still can't forget it.
There wasn't much time for everyone to do
it together.
After all, the stage is a live thing.
The more you pile up, the better you can
do it.
It's okay to look at us as much as you
want, it's okay, it's okay. I remember
that very well.
It's amazing that Satchan became the
captain, and he was like me, but I was
trying my best to become the captain.
That's what I thought when I saw it.
I don't like it. It's embarrassing.
I've never been called like this.
My face is getting red.
It's embarrassing.
Let's move on to the next one. Thank you.
Next, we will introduce Urumi.
Here is Urumi's quote.
This is the phrase that came to my mind.
The tomato called Princess Tomato is very
delicious, so I'll give it to you.
Who would you give it to?
Well, Ogawa-san.
I'm not good at tomatoes.
Even if I'm not good at tomatoes, I
wonder if there is a tomato that I can
overcome.
When I heard it, I immediately said that
there was a sweet tomato called Princess
Tomato, so it was very delicious, so I
said I would give it to you, and it was
really delicious when I ate it right away
and it came out.
It was as sweet as a fruit.
In this small box,
there were tomatoes in every room.
It was so expensive.
When I opened it,
I was like, what is this tomato?
It was in the box.
But I overcame it.
I can only eat princess tomatoes.
I can only eat tomatoes.
That's right.
I'm eating something good.
It's not good from the beginning.
Yes, little by little.
I regularly give Princess Tomatoes.
I can't find it wherever I go.
Where can I buy it?
It's a specialty store.
Sometimes it's sold at the supermarket.
It's also sold at supermarkets.
The ones in every room are only sold at
the specialty stores.
Like Ginza.
Wait, Aya is from Ginza?
Princess Tomato.
Aya is from Ginza?
Really?
At that time, I heard about sweet
tomatoes.
Are there any other recommended tomatoes?
There's one on top, right?
The one on top of the princess is called
Queen.
Queen Tomato?
It's the same one, but there's one in
each.
It's only for summer.
Are you familiar with tomatoes?
That's right.
I came from the tomato kingdom.
That's not what I meant.
It's different.
It's different, right?
In a different show,
I had to leave my impression in the self-
introduction.
I thought about it, and that's all I
could think of.
But Urumi is even worse.
It's like coming from a star in space.
That's right.
It came from a tomato.
It came from a tomato kingdom.
You've been here since you were a child,
haven't you?
Do you have any greetings from the Tomato
Kingdom?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no
Ah, that's true.
Why don't we have the two of you say
goodbye to the Tomato Kingdom?
It's decided!
Even if it's bad...
Okay, thank you very much.
So, that's all for today.
I want some time to think.
That's true.
Well, it's fine if it's just like that.
In the meantime, let's hear your
impressions.
It's the first half. Yuna-san, how was
it?
I thought I was watching Go Kisei a lot,
but I thought that each of them had a
relationship that I didn't know, and I
wanted her to be my younger sister all
the time.
I thought there were a lot of older
sisters.
I'm glad.
Go Kisei.
On the other hand, I wish I could hear
more from my peers, not just my seniors
and juniors.
Even if it's not about the relationship
between the seniors, I want to hear more
about the same-sex relationship between
the seniors.
As a junior, I really want to hear about
the same-sex relationship between the
seniors.
That's right.
There's not much to talk about.
That's right. There's not much to talk
about.
Even if it's not on-air, there's a lot
more, right?
I had a lot more, and I wanted it to be
released somewhere.
That's right.
That's true.
I think it's about time to decide.
I think so, too.
Aya came from the Tomato Kingdom.
She was the one who came from the Kingdom
on her own.
Did you decide?
Yes, I did.
I'm almost done.
Don't you do it, Aya?
I rarely do it.
It's like you're featuring Aya.
Please do it.
That's all for today.
Today, I'd like you two, who came from
the Kingdom of Tomatoes, to close the
show.
I'd like to have it.
Please.
I'll do it.
Pi, pi, pi, pi.
Pi, pi, pi, pi, pi.
Thank you for watching!